https://www.loadtestingtool.com/privacy.shtml

Products
Products:
WAPT
Regular version of WAPT includes all the basic features required to test a web site with up to 2,000 concurrent virtual users.
WAPT Pro
Professional version can use several systems for load generation, remotely control test execution, monitor server performance and handle complex parameterization.
WAPT Cloud
Cloud version of the most powerful load testing solution based on WAPT Pro and all extension modules.
Extensions:
x64 Load Engine
Powerful load generation utility that can be used together with WAPT Pro to create 10,000 and more virtual users per system.
Modules:
ASP.net testing
Enables the automatic parameterization of the view state and event validation values.
JSON format
Enables the automatic parameterization of session-specific values found inside JSON structures and creates formatted JSON representation.
Adobe Flash testing
Converts binary AMF structures used by Flash applications to XML form.
WebSocket testing
Utilizes WebSocket protocol for instant data updates.
PeopleSoft testing
Automates client-set cookies creation in PeopleSoft tests.
Silverlight testing
Converts binary MSBIN structures used by Silverlight applications to XML form.
GWT testing
Converts GWT data to XML structures facilitating work with session-specific values.
Binary formats
Provides the ability to work with the binary data inside the HTTP requests and responses.
SharePoint testing
Parameterizes the form digest values in the headers and request parameters of SharePoint applications.
Services
Configuration consulting
Tell us more about your project and we will provide recommendations on software licenses and hardware configuration required to perform your load test.
Test design service
Need help creating a custom test for a website? We are ready to work with you on the test specification and deliver ready to use source files. Accurate emulation is guaranteed.
Load testing service
Hire us for a full load testing project. Specify the goals and let us design and run the test. Get the complete analysis and recommendations in the report prepared by our QA team.
Download
Pricing
Support
Customer support service
We provide customer support for existing and new customers free of charge. You are welcome to contact us with any questions from pure technical to sales and business opportunities.
Frequently Asked Questions
From choosing components to product functionality and licensing.
Knowledge base
The complete reference on the WAPT Pro user interface and functionality.
Quick Start Guide
A short step by step instruction on how to create a simple but very typical test scenario for a web site, launch the test and interpret its results.
Product update information
Version history and our upgrade policy for existing customers.
Resources
WAPT demo video
This demo clip shows step by step how to design a test with different types of virtual users, perform load testing of a web application, and interpret the test results.
PowerPoint presentation
The fastest way to get familiar with load testing and WAPT key features.
WAPT vs JMeter
7 reasons why you will be better off with WAPT Pro unless zero license cost is your only target.
WAPT vs LoadRunner
How the choice between LoadRunner and WAPT Pro is seen from the new user perspective.
WAPT tools & services overview
Load testing tools and services offered by SoftLogica Inc. A guide for decision-makers.
Clients
Customer testimonials
With more than 3'000 customers worldwide, WAPT is the well-known brand on the performance testing market. Read what our clients have to say about our tools and services.
WAPT user forum
The place where users of our tools discuss their testing challenges and technical solutions.
On Load Testing blog
In-house expertise, best testing practices, product announcements, etc.
Case studies
Patient education - a learning website where people can train their skills.iOS application - an online ticketing system integrated with additional services.Load balancer - an insurance service with up to 10,000 concurrent user sessions.CRM system - a universal bank with broad range of products and services.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SoftLogica Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (the "Users") of the www.loadtestingtool.com website (the "Website").
Personal identification information: We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Website, register on the Website, place orders, subscribe to newsletters, fill out forms, and in connection with other available activities, services or resources. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, etc. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website related activities.
Non-personal identification information: We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies: Our Website may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.
We may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Website.
To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To process payments: We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Website feature.
We may use the email address to send User information pertaining to our services. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, User may contact us.
How we protect your information: We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Webite and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel.
Sharing your personal information: We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.
Third party websites: Users may find advertising or other content on our Website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Website, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Compliance with children's online privacy protection act: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Changes to this privacy policy: SoftLogica Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms: By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at:
SoftLogica Inc.
901 N Pitt str Suite 325, Alexandria, VA, 22314, United States
Phone: 1.888.364.6797
Email: support@loadtestingtool.com
This document was last updated on January 31, 2013.
Products
WAPT
WAPT Pro
x64 Load Engine
WAPT Cloud
Download
Pricing
Modules
On Load Testing blog
Follow us:
Copyright © SoftLogica 2003-2020
Adobe® and Adobe Flash® are trademarks of Adobe Systems Incorporated,PeopleSoft® is a registered trademark of Oracle Corporation,SharePoint® is a registered trademark of Microsoft Corporation.
Home Privacy Policy EULA Contact Us
